<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Day Dreaming]]></title><description><![CDATA[A blog to show my thoughts.]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 06:53:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Start Writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Recently, I’m trying to get myself busier and so I start working on converting some ideas to side projects. I feel like something is missing…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/start-writing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/start-writing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 23:18:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Recently, I’m trying to get myself busier and so I start working on converting some ideas to side projects. I feel like something is missing during busy work, I’m just keep working and coding, but I never have a place to express my feeling about lots of things happened in the past and show people who may encounter some problems, and looking for a solution. For those reason, I picked up this blog again and gave it a shot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had never been a good writer, to be frankly, I’m a shitty writer. I don’t have practices to organize my thoughts and putting them into sentences. This is a practice, a grind for me to rethink myself at my 30s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe nobody will look at this blog, it is fine and I won’t expect anything. But I will continue to write something even little things to produce something in the internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wish me luck!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is my first post on my new blog! How exciting! But also a day I need to remember my grandpa. R.I.P]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/hello-world/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 01:50:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is my first post on my new blog! How exciting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But also a day I need to remember my grandpa. R.I.P&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>