<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Day Dreaming]]></title><description><![CDATA[A blog to show my thoughts.]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 07:27:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Golf Impact Position]]></title><description><![CDATA[Golf 10 months milestone
I had started serious golfing for about 10 months. During this period, I had learnt a lot about swing and gotten…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/golf-impact/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/golf-impact/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 07:25:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Golf 10 months milestone&lt;/strong&gt;
I had started serious golfing for about 10 months. During this period, I had learnt a lot about swing and gotten obsessed with golfing. It could be a new thing to keep me busy and mental healthy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After those months, I can play like a normal golfer in the course, and made my first birdie of my life. It is the perfect game when I’m getting older since playing soccer or tennis is too intense for me. I also look back to some tutorials I visited before and I just realized I should go back to fundamental thing about my swing — impact position&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impact Position&lt;/strong&gt;
Impact position is the position when your club face meets the ball during the swing. It is the only most important part on how good a player hits the ball. I recently had lots of pushes when I’m hitting balls, so I decide to step back and mastering the impact position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To master impact position, I believe there are serval steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;swing at 50% speed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;swinging at a slower speed, so I can feel what I should do with my body. Also I know stop and posing on a static position won’t give me the feel. In a slower speed, I can still connect all positions(p0, p1, p2…) and also muscle memorize the impact position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel what the impact position is&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What I’m doing is go to the impact position before I’m doing anything&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adjust my body to impact position&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are 2 things I’m checking: hip and arm position&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hip should be about 20-30 degree turned to left&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Because of keeping club face square, so left arm needs to go a little bit forward and left to stay in the swing plane&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep practicing it for a month&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Changing swing is pretty easy, but make it work takes time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I know it is the right move, so I need to make it work on driving range&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take it to the golf course&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practicing in driving range is always different than swing in the actual course&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Swing in actual course is kinda like final exam when you are learning a course&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The grass is less forgiving than the mat always :)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today is my first day to practice the impact position drill with Irons and Driver. Irons went pretty well, but I still didn’t quite understand what the drivers impact position is. So I found an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HR3kL8PpHd4&quot;&gt;video for driver impact drill&lt;/a&gt;. I’m going to try it in my next practice session.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Golf is hard and keep grind!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Start Writing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Recently, I’m trying to get myself busier and so I start working on converting some ideas to side projects. I feel like something is missing…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/start-writing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/start-writing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 23:18:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Recently, I’m trying to get myself busier and so I start working on converting some ideas to side projects. I feel like something is missing during busy work, I’m just keep working and coding, but I never have a place to express my feeling about lots of things happened in the past and show people who may encounter some problems, and looking for a solution. For those reason, I picked up this blog again and gave it a shot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had never been a good writer, to be frankly, I’m a shitty writer. I don’t have practices to organize my thoughts and putting them into sentences. This is a practice, a grind for me to rethink myself at my 30s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe nobody will look at this blog, it is fine and I won’t expect anything. But I will continue to write something even little things to produce something in the internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wish me luck!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is my first post on my new blog! How exciting! But also a day I need to remember my grandpa. R.I.P]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/hello-world/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 01:50:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is my first post on my new blog! How exciting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But also a day I need to remember my grandpa. R.I.P&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>